No, seriously, really.
いや、マジで本当に
I couldn't find it when we first met.
見つからなかったもん、最初待ち合わせした時
Really.
本当に
what happened?
どうしたの?
picture?
え?
I'm thinking about getting a job.
就職しようかなって
picture?
え?
find work?
就職?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
What is that?
なにそれ?
Are you swimming?
泳いでんの?
No, get a job?
いや、就職?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
No, you don't have to say something stupid like that.
いや、そんな馬鹿なこと言わなくていい
picture?
え?
Are you really saying that?
本当に言ってんの?
Are you going to get a job?
就職するの?
picture?
え?
Have you decided yet?
もう決まったの?
It's decided.
決まった
picture?
え?
What series?
何系?
secret?
秘密?
I can't say that.
それは言えないよね
Seriously?
マジか?
Did you get a job?
就職したんだ?
Are you still young?
まだ若いのに?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Good find.
よく見つけたね
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Did you go to the interview with blonde hair?
髪の毛、金髪の状態で面接いったの?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't that so?
それはないか
Did you cut it?
切っちゃったの?
I've graduated.
卒業しちゃったんだ
nice.
いいね
Isn't it fashionable from top to bottom?
それは上から下に お洒落でしょ?
But will I cut it again?
でもまた切るの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫なの?
The color of that hair.
その 髪の毛の色
Somewhat.
若干
I mean, it's a little bright.
だって、 ちょっと明るいよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Should I cut it?
切るの?
Also.
また
What should I do?
どうすんの?
Should I make it black?
黒にするの?
Are you going to make it all black?
真っ黒にするの?
It's not pitch black.
真っ黒じゃない
Well, if it were that color.
まあ、でもその色だったらね
Especially if it was something like Gem Inn.
別 にジェムインとかだったらね
It's okay.
大丈夫だもんね
picture?
え?
It's very cloudy.
めっちゃ曇ってんじゃん
Get into the hot water.
お 湯の中入って
I'll use my fingers for a while.
指ね、ちょっとつかろう
It's getting really dark.
めっちゃ黒くなってんね
This black is lukewarm.
ぬるい、この黒
picture?
え?
Was it really cloudy?
めっちゃ曇っちゃった?
Because it's really lukewarm.
めっちゃからぬるいから
A little lukewarm.
ちょっとぬるい
How do you get in?
こうやって入るの?
hot?
暑い?
It's really hot though.
め っちゃ暑いけど
Do you want to sleep?
ねるかって
picture?
え?
It warmed me up.
温まった
Have you warmed up?
温まっちゃった?
Was it a feeling?
気持ちだった?
Hokkoya.
ほっこや
It's so warm.
ほっこやな
Then let's go.
じゃあ行こうか
Go around outside.
外で回って
You can't really see it?
めっちゃまで見えない?
Very
めっちゃ
Can't you see until?
まで 見えない?
Can I do it to you?
お前にしていい?
Are you serious?
本気?
Are you not serious?
本気のないの?
Why don't you know?
なんで知らないの?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
恥ずかしいんだよね
why?
なんで?
なん で?
How does it get so hot?
どうやってこんなに暑くなるの?
When?
どういうとき?
Did you drink alcohol?
お酒飲んだの?
お酒飲んだっけ?
After?
あと?
The rest...
あとはなんか...
After?
あと?
How cool are you?
どんなに涼しくしてるの?
Oh no, you don't want to talk.
やべ、話す気ないじゃん
why?
なんで?
here we go.
さ あ
Isn't it difficult when other people are watching?
やっぱ人が見てると難しい?
Yes, I don't like it.
そう、嫌だ
I hope I'm alone.
一人だといいんだけど
I'll be alone, then.
一人になるよ、俺じゃあ
Shall we go somewhere?
ちょっとどっか行っちゃう?
Okay, I'll go somewhere.
いいよ、どっか行っちゃうよ
How can I do that?
どうしたらできるの?
Really?
本当に?
I'll watch it, so do it.
見ててあげるからやって
Look at it!
見んじゃやべ
Please go out.
お出かけしてきなよ
Did you go out?
お出かけしてくれた?
Outing for the bottom.
お下の出かけ
Well then, I'm going to stay in the bathroom for a while.
じゃあちょっとトイレにこもってるね
Yeah.
うん
It's okay to be hungry.
おなけっていいよ
picture?
え?
It went up.
あがった
Play music.
音楽かけて
I'll bring it back in 5 minutes.
5分後も持ってくるから
5 minutes later?
5分後?
picture?
え?
Is it finished?
終わったの?
It was over.
終わってた
I heard 8.
8って聞こえたよ
Isn't it early?
早くない?
It's not too early.
早 くないよ
Did it feel good?
気持ちかった?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Ojinpo?
おじんぽ?
I want Ojinpo.
おじんぽ欲しい
I want a baby.
お じんぽ欲しい
what?
なに?
Can I take this?
これを取っていいの?
Let me take it out.
抜かせて
I can't ignore that.
それって抜かせないですね
thank you.
ありがとう
Panpon.
パンポン
Panpon?
パンポン?
Panpon.
パンポン
Pump pong pong pompon?
パンポンパンポンパンポンポンポン?
why?
なんで?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Try licking it with the skin on.
皮をかぶった状態で舐めてみて
This will grow.
これ伸びる
Lick it.
舐めて
Tsumega.
つめが
quick.
はやく
What do you think?
どうでしょう?
Okay.
よし
Lick it good.
いいの舐めて
Leave it like this?
このまま?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
Is it wrong to put a curve in it?
カーブ入れてダメなの?
yes.
そう
For now
とりあえ
figure.
ず
I don't know.
分 からない
I don't know?
分からない?
Would you like to sit down for a while?
ちょっと座らないかな?
Yeah.
うん
a little bit
ちょっと
You won't sit down.
座 らないでしょ
It's no good if you make a noise like that.
そんな、鳴るとダメだよ
It came out again.
また出た
You won't write it.
書かないでしょ
It's no good if it rings.
鳴るとダメ
Yeah.
うん
This guy.
こいつ
this?
これ?
Does that bother you?
それ邪魔なの?
That bothers me.
それ邪魔
Is it bad if it rings?
鳴るとダメ?
It's here.
ここだよね
A little ice cream.
ちょっとアイスクリーム
Ice cream?
アイスクリーム?
where?
どこ?
This is ice cream.
これアイスクリーム
This is it.
これね
hey?
ね?
perhaps.
たぶん
Later, while walking around unable to speak.
あとで喋れずに回りながら
Yeah.
うん
My hair is no good.
髪の毛が駄目だよ
Okay,
よし、
So let's touch it.
じゃあ 触ろう
yeah?
ん?
copper?
どう?
This is locked.
これロック入ってるよ
hot.
熱い
copper?
どう?
hot?
熱い?
hot.
熱い
copper?
どう?
hot?
熱い?
hot.
熱い
It's in, great.
入ってるよ、すごい
hot.
熱い
Can you see it?
見えちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
It's really in there.
すげえ入ってるよ
copper?
どう?
Chinchi.
ちんち
hot.
熱い
Let's go.
いっちゃい
hot?
熱い?
hot.
熱い
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Then I'll figure it out myself.
じゃあ自分がくりいじって
Yes, yes, yes.
そう、そう、そう
Play around with what feels good.
気持ちいいとこいじってて
We'll feel good together.
一緒に気持ちよくなる
Yeah.
うん
I feel terrible.
やばい気持ち
Yeah.
うん
I feel like I'm going to go too far.
あんまりいっちゃいそうになる
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel good there?
そ こが気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん
This is included.
これ入ってるよ
hey?
ね?
My dick is in there right now.
すぐちんち入ってるよ
hot.
熱い
It's hot.
熱いね
The back?
奥が?
Yeah.
うん
Is it better at the back?
奥の方がいい?
It's better in the back.
奥の方がいい
I feel like I'm going to go crazy when the back part is opened.
奥の方がくりいちゃうといっちゃいそうになる
Yes, that's right.
はい、そう
What should I do?
どうすればいい?
I understand.
分かる
But I want to go with a Rolls Royce.
でもロールスロイスでいきたいんだよね
Yeah.
うん
I want to go with Boobs Royce.
ブーブスロイスでいきたい
Yeah.
うん
Damn it, it's going to be really scary.
あぶねー、めっちゃいそうになっちゃう
hot.
熱い
Yeah.
うん
It's hot.
熱っ
I'm going to go crazy.
ぐっきりいっちゃうよ
Yeah.
うん
Okay, then let's go quickly.
よっしゃ、じゃあはやくいっちゃうよ
Yeah.
うん
I don't understand
わから
weird.
へ ん
I don't know.
わ からへん
It was really intense at the end.
最後めっちゃ激しかった
I don't understand.
わからへん
how was it?
どうだった?
最後
It's already too intense, it just happened in a moment.
もう激しすぎてもう、 一瞬の出来事
Wait a minute, look.
ちょっと待って、見てくれ
It was slippery, muddy, and slippery.
どろどろどろ、どろどろ、滑れてきた
why?
なんで?
It's disgusting
気持ち悪くて
together together together
一 緒に一緒に
Ah, I'm already asleep
あー、 もう寝ちゃった
hot
熱 い
I fell asleep with these deep tears, deep tears What?
この 奥の涙 奥の涙じゃ寝ちゃった 何?
I want to go in a slow chair too I want to go in a slow chair too
僕もスローイスで行きたいんだよね 僕もスローイスで行きたい
Let's enjoy the cherry blossoms and go.
桜 をすらすり、いっちゃうぜ
Oh no, hey, there it was!
いやー、ちょー、あった!
I'm going to go suri-suri soon.
そろそろすらすりでいってくるわ
The solo slow pose.
ソロースロースのポーズがね
Not yet, hey.
まだ、ちょー、わ
It's okay, okay, okay, I'm here.
なったね、よっしゃ、よっしゃ、いってる
Mr. Detake.
でーたけさん
What do you have?
それ、何持ってるの?
picture?
え?
What do you have?
何持ってるの?
Huh?
あれ?
Oh, what happened to that?
おお、どうしよったのそれ
What happened?
どうしよったの?
What happened to that?
どうしたのそれ?
picture?
え?
What is that?
何それ?
Toy?
お もちゃ?
Ah, toys.
あ、おもちゃ
Toys?
おもちゃ?
toys.
おもちゃ
It looks like a dick.
ちんちんみたいだね
That's amazing, that's amazing.
すごい、すごいなそれ
Well, this is amazing.
えっと、すごいなこれ
Wow, it's so soft.
おーすげー、柔らかいね
Yeah.
うん
Do you like this?
これ好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
Do you like this?
これ好き?
Yeah.
うん
Do you like it?
好きなの?
long time no see.
久しぶり
How have you been?
元気だった?
Yeah.
うん
Really.
本当に
It's been a really long time.
めっちゃ久しぶりだよね
yes.
そう
oh yeah.
そうそう
I just couldn't find anything today.
ちょっとあの、まじ見つけられなかった今日
Yes, I was doing well.
そう、なんか元気通りをしたの
W-what happened?
な、 な、どうした?
What happened?
何があったの?
Really.
本当に
I had really blonde hair before, and it was curly, but...
なんかもう、前すげー金髪でさ、 くっくる巻きだったけどさ、
What happened?
何があったの?
Make it the owner?
オーナーにする?
picture?
え?
Did you become an owner today?
今日オーナーにした?
I don't own it today.
オーナーにしてない、今日
When did you do it?
いつしたの?
recently.
最近
Well, when was that?
えーと、いつだっけ?
I don't want it to take a day.
1日かかるくない
Did it last for about a day?
1日ぐらいまでしちゃったの?
Yeah.
うん
No, but that's fine.
いや、でもいいね
It's Hello Kitty today.
今日キティちゃんだね
Kitty?
キティ?
Hey, it's Hello Kitty today.
ねぇ、今日はキティちゃんだね
It was a melody before.
前メロだったけど
No, it really has changed.
いや、ほんと変わったね
No, hair color changes a lot of people.
いや、髪色ってすごい人変わるね
Hairstyle?
髪型?
Um, her hair was cut a little.
あの、髪型もちょっと髪切ったやつ
Ah, that's right.
あぁ、そうなんだ
No, but it's been a while.
いや、でも久しぶり
Are you wet?
濡れてる?
picture?
え?
Are you wet?
濡れてる?
濡れてんの?
Are you wet?
濡れてる?
No, not yet.
いや、まだです
Not wet yet?
まだ濡れてない?
That's right.
そうだよね
But wouldn't it get wet if I touched it?
でもそれ触ったら濡れてくちゃうんじゃないの?
Am I not wet?
俺、湿ってない?
this.
これ
picture?
え?
Is it damp?
湿ってる?
why?
なんで?
Have you used it?
使っちゃったの?
I haven't used it though.
使ってないけど
It's naughty, really.
エッチだね、ほんとに
You have bare skin today.
今日、お素肌だね
You don't wear two glasses.
二杯履かないんだね
I don't wear them at all.
履かないよ、二杯は
Are the insides of your pants dirty today?
今日パンツの裏は汚れてる?
Not dirty.
汚れてない
real?
ほんと?
Now, make the heel a little M-shaped.
じゃあ、ヒール、ちょっとM字にして
Isn't it dirty?
汚れてないの?
It's not dirty.
汚れてないよ
Seriously?
マジか
I wish it was dirty.
汚れててほしかったな
Isn't it dirty?
汚れてないの?
Not dirty.
汚れてない
Make it the owner?
オーナーにする?
picture?
え?
Did you become an owner today?
今日、オーナーにした?
I don't own it today.
オーナーにしてない、今日
When did you do it?
いつしたの?
recently.
最近
Well, when was that?
えっと、いつだっけ?
I don't want to hang it for a moment.
一瞬掛けたくない
Did you do it for a moment?
一瞬ぐらいまでしてたの?
I haven't.
してない
picture?
え?
What kind of owner will you have?
どんなオーナーにするの?
Gee until it comes out normally.
普通に出るまでジーって
Can you guess G?
ジーって当てちゃうの?
What do you say when you go?
行くとき何て言うの?
Say you're going.
行くって言う
Are you saying you're going?
行っちゃうって言うの?
Are you saying you go even when you're alone?
一人でいるときも行くって言うの?
When you're alone?
一人でいるとき?
Will you shut up?
黙っちゃう?
Yeah, I'm silent.
うん、黙ってる
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
But what do you do when something like this happens for a moment?
でも一瞬こうなってどうすんの?
Oh, are you saying you're going?
あ、行きそうって言うの?
Hey, here.
ね、ここで
Here, like this.
ここであ、こうやって
What, are you saying that?
え、言うの?
Really?
本当に?
Are you really saying that?
本当に言うの?
Ah, ah, you say that?
あ、あ、あって言う?
Oh, you say you're going?
あ、行くって言う?
Yeah.
うん
Do you say it?
言うの?
TRUE?
本当?
say, say
言う、言う
Seriously?
マジか
That's amazing, that's perverted.
すごいね、変態だね
Last time, for the first time, only Nakata was robbed.
前回さ、初めてさ、中田しか奪っちゃったんだよね
Yes, for the first time.
そう、初めて
How is today?
今日はいい?
picture?
え?
Until I steal a little today.
今日もちょっと奪くまで
Okay.
いいよ
Can I take it out?
出しちゃっていい?
Okay.
いいよ
Is it okay?
いい の?
Okay.
いいよ
Will you do it?
やっちゃうよ?
Is it okay for the first time?
初めていい?
Yeah.
うん
There are lots of toys today.
今日はね、おもちゃいっぱいあるからさ
Yeah.
うん
Today, I brought this guy, this guy, this guy.
今日はさ、こいつ、こいつ、こいつ連れてきたからさ
Eh, this.
え、これ
This guy.
こいつ
Well, I think this is really bad.
え、これやっぱやばいと思う
That's amazing.
それすげえよ
Is this how you use it?
これこうやって使うやつ?
Yeah, yeah, that's how you do it.
そうそうそう、そうやってやるやつ
Yes, I understand.
そう、よくわかったね
How did you know?
なんでわかったの?
Huh, doesn't it look kind of poppy?
え、なんか、なんかぽっぽくない?
here.
ここ
Yeah, yeah, that, that, that.
そうそうそう、それ、それ、それ
That's because this guy also has it.
それ、 こいつもあるから
What is that?
それ、何?
There's this one too.
こいつもある
friend.
友達
friend?
友達?
My friend.
マイフレンド
My friend?
マイフレンド?
This too.
これも
So let's take off the mask.
じゃあちょっとマスク取っていこうか
No, I like it.
いや、いいね
Open, without a mask.
マスクなしの、開いて
What should I do?
どうする?
toys.
おもちゃ
No, I can't get it like this.
いや、こう、つかないんだけど
I'd rather not have a mask.
マスクない方がいいよ
She's cuter without the mask.
マスクない方が可愛い
It's going to be someone.
誰かに出るんだよね
go out to someone
誰かに出る
That's what I'm told.
言われるよね
I wonder who it is.
誰だろうなぁ
Do you want to do that soon?
早くそれでやってほしい?
What, did you break it?
え、壊したの?
Oh, wait, I broke it.
え、待って、壊した
Just closed it.
閉じただけで
Oh, I was surprised.
おぉ、びっくりした
Well then, let's take some clothes off.
じゃあ、ちょっと脱いでいこうかな
Maybe I should take it off.
脱いでいっちゃおうかな
Shall I take my clothes off?
脱 いでいきます?
So, take it off and do like this one.
じゃあ、脱いでこいつものように
Eh, is it okay to stay like that?
え、その状態でいいの?
Can't you take it off in this state?
この状態で脱げなくない?
come off?
脱げる?
Can't take it off?
脱げない?
I can't take it off.
脱げません
Okay.
いいよ
Let's take it off.
脱いじゃおう
Well, when I was in high school,
なんかさ、俺がさ、高校の時のさ、
You look like your teacher.
先生に似てんだよね
gentlemen?
先生?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Do you look like that age?
そんな歳に似てる?
English teacher.
英語の先生
Well, I'm glad that person was young.
いやいや、その人若かったよさ
You were young.
若かったね
So when I was 18, oh, no, I'm not 18.
じゃあ、俺が18の時に、 あ、違う18じゃない、
When I was 17, my teacher was probably 20.
17の時に、 その先生が多分20ね、
There were about 2 or 3.
2、3くらいあったの
Yes, it's similar.
そう、似てる
He's speaking English.
英語喋ってるって
He speaks English.
英語喋るんだよ
picture?
え?
Like hello.
ハローみたいな
halo?
ハロー?
halo.
ハロー
halo?
ハロー?
English teachers look alike.
英語の先生、似てる
No, it's because I chose that hair color.
いや、その髪色にしたからだよ
Well, when I looked like a gal, it was completely different.
いや、ギャルっぽかった時は全然違うんだけど、
Yes, that teacher has black hair, and it's about that long.
そう、その先生、黒髪でさ、 そんぐらいの長さなんだよね
nice.
いいね
Okay, then why don't you take it off?
いいよ、じゃあ、脱ぐ?
Oh, that's right, those clothes...
あ、それ、そう、その服がね、ちょっとね、
It's so baggy.
ぶかぶかなんだよ
sorry.
すみません
No, this position too.
いや、この体勢もね
Yes, wait a minute.
はい、ちょっと待って
I like this.
いいね、これ
How much did this cost?
いくらしたの、これ?
What should I do?
どう する?
How many people will I bring this lens to first come first served?
これ先着何名様に連れレンズする?
No, I won't.
いや、あげません
Okay, then.
いいよ、じゃあ
Stand up and take it off?
立って脱ぐ?
Stand up and take off your clothes.
立って脱ぐ
I can't take it off.
私、脱げないよ
Well, the clothes on top of that are the same as before.
あれ、その上の服、一緒やねん、前も
What?
何が?
You also shaved your hair.
お前も髪剃るだったよね
Well, it makes my stomach hurt, but...
え、だってお腹痛くするけど、だって
What?
え、何?
Oh, it's too cold?
あ、寒すぎて?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Well then, okay.
じゃあ、いいよ
Can't you stand properly?
ちゃんと立たぬの?
yeah?
ん?
Why don't you stand up, Kitty?
立たぬのかよ、キティちゃん
I can't stand.
立たないの
what?
何?
Now.
今の
What, can I stand?
え、立っていいの?
Do you want to stand?
立ちたい?
I want to stand up.
立ちたいよ
Okay, then let me make my dick stand up too.
いいよ、じゃあ、俺のチンコも立たせる
Yes, recently, my eyes have gotten bigger.
そう、なんか最近さ、なんか目で大きくなったんだよね
Mochi, didn't you learn that?
もち、それ学んでってなかった?
No, I haven't.
いや、やってない
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
You're still young.
まだ、まだ若いからね
Because I'm still young.
まだ若いから
Because it's ticklish, it's ticklish.
だって、くすぐったい、くすぐったい
It's ticklish, it's ticklish.
くすぐったい、くすぐったい
Oh no, because I'm stuffing it, and it hurts.
やばい、だって詰めるから、痛くする
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い、痛い、痛い
No, it's not good at all.
いや、全然、全然いいじゃん
lie?
う そ?
Maybe it's because I'm hunched over.
猫背だからかな
Are you hunched over?
猫背なの?
She looks like a model, though.
モデルっぽいよ、でも
Because I didn't have a hunched back.
猫背なかったからね
Look around, then.
よく向いて、じゃあ
picture?
え?
Look well.
よく向いて
Not at all.
全然だよ
What should I do?
どうすか?
What do you all think?
皆さんどう思います?
If anyone sees this.
これをもし見る人がいたら
You're not thin at all.
全然痩せてるよね
It's just right.
ちょうどいいんだよ
Is it just right?
ちょうどいい?
Yeah.
うん
There's still a neck, at the neck.
まだ首がある、首で
It has a neck, absolutely.
首があるよ、全然
nice.
いいね
My back is, like, this thing.
背中が、なんかね、このなんつーの
Do you understand this?
このさ、分かるかな?
This line.
このライン
Well then, take a look at the side.
じゃあ、横ちゃんと見て
Huh?
あれ?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Is this what's going on?
こうなってんの?
That's it.
サーッつって
Do you understand?
分かるかな?
Saaaaat.
サーッって
Are you feeling relieved?
サーッとなってるの?
Come on, wait a minute.
こうきて、ちょっと待ってね
It came from a standing position, came like this, and became a whoosh.
立てからきて、こうきて、シューってなってる
Look.
ほら
Awesome.
すげー
Ah, nice.
あーいいね
Ah, good.
あーいい
Good this.
いいこれ
This is amazing.
すげーいいこれ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
There are so many.
めっちゃあるよ
Look at my legs sticking out my ass.
お尻プッてる足見て
oh yeah.
そうそう
Front, ass, look at me, look at me.
前、ケツ、こう、俺見て、俺見て
Like this.
こんな感じで
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
That's that.
それそれそれ
What do you think?
どうどうどうどうどう
What are you doing?
何してんの?
different.
違う
Look at me, look at me, look at me.
俺見て、俺見て、俺見て
Shall we go?
いくよ?
This, this, this, this.
これ、これ、これ、これ
I've never done anything like that so I don't know.
そんなことやったことないから分からないんだよ
And it feels like my butt is out.
で、お尻出す感じ
Ah, yes, that's it.
あ、そう、それそれ
Give it a little more force.
それもうちょっとグイって出して
It feels like my butt is sticking out.
お尻出す感じ
Oh, that's it, I like that.
あ、それそれ、俺それ好き
I like that.
それ好き
nice.
いいね
Wow, wow.
うわ、やば
I'm going to make a roll sloice today.
今日ロールスローイスやってくからね
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
You're used to it now, right?
もう慣れたでしょ?
Are you used to it?
慣れた?
I got used to it.
慣れた
Have you grown up?
大きくなったの?
Really.
ほんとに
You know, I've really grown up, really.
ね、ほんと大きくなった、ほんと
I won't know unless I touch it underground.
地下で触らないと分からないけど
Underground?
地下で?
Can I touch you underground?
地下で触っていいの?
Okay.
いいよ
picture?
え?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Yeah.
うん
This nail?
こっちくぎ?
This is this nail?
こっちくぎこれ?
Here, here, here.
こっちこっちこいっか
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
When you touch Sukugi, it feels hot again, right?
すくぎ触るとまた熱い熱いって言うんでしょ?
different.
違う
I want to eat it.
食うたい
picture?
え?
Do you want to eat?
食うたいの?
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
Just a little bit.
ちょっとちょっと
Yeah?
うん?
Ah, but it might have gotten bigger.
あ、でも大きくなったかもね
Right?
でしょ?
Ah, this is nice.
あ、いいねこれちょっと
good.
いい
This is amazing.
すげえいいこれ
nice.
いいね
Who looks similar?
誰が似てんだよな
I wonder who it is.
誰だろうな
There is a line that seems to show a little bit of breasts but is invisible.
おっぱいちょっと見えそうで見えないラインが
Awesome.
すげえ
It's spacious.
広いね
this?
これ?
what?
何?
this?
これ?
yeah?
ん?
What is this?
これ何?
This is so cute.
これちくぎ
Chikugi?
ちくぎ?
I couldn't tell you about my clitoris before.
前はクリトリスをさ、言えなかったのにさ、
I said it eventually.
言ったんだけど最終的に
It's so beautiful.
すげえ綺麗だね
Look here.
見るよここ
Look at this.
これ見て
copper?
どう?
See for yourself.
自分で見て
Yeah.
うん
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, isn't it beautiful?
え、綺麗でしょ?
So beautiful.
そう綺麗
Oh, it's so beautiful.
え、すごい綺麗だよね
Well, I took a picture.
じゃあ、撮っちゃった
picture?
え?
Okay.
いいよ
Wow.
わお
I took a picture.
撮っちゃったね
撮っちゃった
Eh, nice.
え、いいね
That's some kind of shorts.
そのなんか短パン
It's summer.
夏だね
Well, I did it.
じゃあ、やったよ
Butt pudding.
お尻プって
Also?
また?
Look what I mean.
なんていうか見て
Yes, look at that.
そう、それ見て
See you again.
またかよ
Ah, that's good.
あ、それ、それがいいんだよ
What should I do?
どうしよう
That's amazing.
すげえな
Ah, that's fine.
あ、いいんだよな、それ
Can't you show your butt?
お尻出せないの?
Please.
プって
No, you really know but you just don't do it.
いや、ほんと分かってんのにやらないだけでしょ、
that.
それ
No, really.
違うよ、ほんと
It's true.
ほんとだって
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
I understand.
分かる
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
Okay, then.
いいよ、じゃあ
Should I remove the bottom too?
下も抜いちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going to pull it out all of a sudden?
もういきなり抜っちゃう?
With spandex.
スパンポンで
Is that enough?
もういいの?
Do you want to be?
なりたい?
I want to be
なりたい
picture?
え?
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
Hey, why do you lie?
ねえ、なぜって嘘つくの?
What a lie?
なに嘘?
It's really beautiful, after all.
すごい綺麗だ、やっぱり
Awesome.
すげえ
As expected, it's amazing.
やっぱり、すげえ
For a moment, there it was.
ちょっと、あったあった
What?
え、なに?
cold.
冷たい
Hey, can you wait a second?
ちょっと、ちょっとだめかい?
what?
なに?
cold.
冷たい
cold?
冷たい?
It's really cold.
ほんと冷たい
It's slow, so slow.
ゆっくりだから、ゆっくり
I'll go slowly and slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり行くから
No, no, it feels like it's coming.
違う違う、来てる感じが
As soon as possible.
すぐなりば
Well then, don't move.
じゃあ、動かないで
Don't move.
動かないで
cold.
冷たい
picture?
え?
Amazing, this.
すげえ、これ
Well then, please sit down.
じゃあ、座って下さい
It's cold.
冷たいよ
It might be amazing.
すごいかもしれない
Not really.
ないな
Because it has a lens.
レンズついてるからさ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
what?
なに?
Hey, it's cold.
ねえ、冷たい
ねえ、冷たいよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
cold.
冷たい
Hey, hey.
ちょっと、ちょっと
Why?
なんでだよ
cold.
冷たい
Cold, cold, cold.
冷たい、冷たい、冷たい
cold?
冷たい?
It's cold.
冷たいよ
Well then, let's go to sleep.
じゃあ、寝ちゃおうか
But let's go to sleep at once.
でも、一気に寝ちゃおう
Should I go to sleep at once?
一気に寝ちゃおうか
Okay.
いいよ
picture?
え?
What?
え、なに?
Wait, what are you doing?
ちょっと、なにやってんの?
No pants.
パンツだめだって
Just put your pants back on.
ちょっと、パンツだけ戻して
What is that?
なにそれ?
Why should I fall asleep all at once?
なんで一気に寝ちゃおうか
No, it's okay to fall asleep.
いえいえ、それも寝ちゃっていいです
So sit down for a second.
じゃあ、ちょっと座って
Be safe.
無事になって
What is this way of taking off?
なにこの脱ぎ方?
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見た
Is there a way to take this off?
これ、脱ぎ方あんの?
It's okay because it's cold.
冷たいから大丈夫
This is cold.
これ、 冷えてるよ
what?
なに?
It's cold.
冷えてるよ
picture?
え?
Is your body cold?
体、冷えちゃった?
Yeah.
うん
Not yet, just a little.
まだだよ、ちょっと
Well, not yet.
あれや、まだだな
This, just here.
これ、ちょっと、ここさ
I have to see how tired you are today.
今日のお疲れ具合も見なきゃいけないからさ
How tired are you?
お疲れ具合?
picture?
え?
The pants.
パンツのさ
Ah, nice, pussy.
あ、いいね、おまんち
Pussy.
おまんぽ
Pussy, okay.
おまんぽ、いいよ
Here, my pussy.
ここ、おまんぽ
Yeah.
うん
Is this place good?
ここがいいの?
Pussy.
おまんぽ
I'll go right away.
いきなり行くからね
That's because it's happening all of a sudden.
それ、いきなり行くんだからね
That's strong, isn't it?
強いんだよね、それ
Hey, that's strong.
ねえ、強いんだよ、それ
copper?
どう?
Yeah.
うん
copper?
どう?
Don't you feel better?
気持ちよくなってこない?
While watching that AV a little while ago,
さっきの、ほら、ちょっとあのAVを見ながら、
Just remember it in your head.
頭にちょっと思い出して
It's such a naughty, naughty feeling.
あんなエッチな、エッチな感じでしょ
Look.
ほら
what?
何?
Open it.
開いて
what?
何?
It's like I'm raping the teacher.
なんか先生を犯してるみたいな
Really.
本当に
Hey, you're strong.
ねえ、強いよ
You.
おまえ
It's itchy here.
ここ、痒そう
Red suits you.
赤が合ってるよ
lie.
嘘
Does it itch?
痒いの?
It's not itchy.
痒くないの
Is that so?
そうなの?
Hey, hey.
ねえ、ねえ
yeah?
ん?
what?
何?
what up?
どうした?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Somehow, it's very accurate.
なんか、凄く当てる
Where?
どこが?
yeah?
ん?
where?
どこ?
Open it a little.
ちょっと開いて
Oh, wait, that's impossible.
え、待って、無理
Open it properly.
ちゃんと開いて
Wait, what can't you do?
待って、何ができないの?
What can't you do?
何ができないの?
It just closes.
ただ、閉じちゃうんだよね
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
picture?
え?
it hurts?
痛い?
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
Be honest, tell me if it hurts.
正直に、痛かったら言って
Wait, it's really hot.
待って、凄い暑い
hot?
暑い?
If it hurts, tell me, it really is.
痛かったら言って、本当に
Yeah, it doesn't hurt.
うん、痛くない
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Yeah.
うん
Now on my own feet.
もう、自分の足で
Open it properly.
開いて、ちゃんと
Hold your own hand.
自分で手を押さえて
Hold your hands properly.
手を押さえて、ちゃんと
Hold the left and right sides properly.
左右をちゃんと押さえて
Why?
何で?
I can go, I can go.
いける、いける
Open it properly.
ちゃんと開いて
What, next?
え、次?
I'll make it stronger.
強くしちゃうよ
picture?
え?
It's very accurate.
凄く当たってる
picture?
え?
It's right.
あたってるよ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
copper?
どう?
That's right.
当たってるよ
It's hitting, it's hitting.
あたってる、あたってる
Look, you're right.
ほら、当たってるよ
That's amazing, you're right.
凄いよ、当たってるよ
Being strong is stupid.
強いって、バカは
Close it properly.
ちゃんと閉めて
Yes, it's impossible now.
はい、もう、無理無理
Open, open.
開いて、開いて
Close it for a moment.
ちょっと閉めて
It doesn't feel good.
気持ちよくないって
It feels good though.
気持ちいけどさ
It feels good in the bath.
お風呂で気持ちいいね
This is terrible.
やばいよ
It's scary, but it's kind of hot.
やばいけど、なんか暑い
people are dancing
人が踊ってる
Because it's really hot.
だってめっちゃ暑い
No.
だめだよ
I have to open it properly.
ちゃんと開いてないと
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
え、待って待って待って
It was open.
開いてたよ
Got it.
分かった
I won't open it for a while.
ちょっともう開かないから
Us too.
俺らも
Because it won't open.
開かないからって
We will also be forced to open it.
俺らも強制的に開いちゃう
Oh, wait.
え、待って
No, it's super hot.
いや、なんか超暑い
Well, before I take a bath, before I take a bath,
じゃあさ、お風呂入る前のさ、 お風呂入る前のさ、
I think I'll take a look inside your pussy at Kusuko.
くすこでおまんくんの中見ちゃおうかな
This is terrible.
やばいよ
Oh, wait.
え、待って
That's really impossible.
本当に無理それ
Open more.
もっと開いて
Because it's not open.
開いてないから
Wait, that's really impossible.
待って、本当に無理
Oh, I'm really sleepy.
え、本当に眠い
What will happen?
どうなっちゃうの?
picture?
え?
What will happen?
どうなっちゃうの?
It's a different street.
なんか違う通り
Also?
また?
Are you lost?
迷いっか?
Hey, really.
ねえ、本当にね
That's terrible.
やばいって
Oh, wait.
え、待って
picture?
え?
Oh, wait.
え、待って
What will happen?
どうなっちゃうの?
So I guess I'll go somewhere else.
だから違うとこ行っちゃうとか
Go.
行って
Let's go somewhere different.
違うとこ行ってみよう
Let's go today.
今日は行ってみよう
今日は行こう
Why?
何で?
I won't come there again.
そ こでまた来ないじゃん
No.
ダメだよ
Let's go today.
今日は行ってみよう
It's really impossible.
本当に無理
Are you going somewhere else?
違うとこ行く?
I'll go somewhere else.
違うとこ行っちゃう
Really, already.
本当にね、もう
It hurts, doesn't it hurt?
痛いよ、痛くない?
it hurts.
痛い
TRUE?
本当?
Really?
本当は?
It hurts.
痛いよ
it hurts?
痛い?
Oh, wait.
え、待って
It's impossible.
無理無理な
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
But does it hurt?
でも痛い?
picture?
え?
it hurts?
痛い?
It doesn't hurt though.
痛くないけど
Are you going somewhere strange?
変なとこ行っちゃうの?
Yeah.
うん
I'm going to a different hotel.
違うホテル行っちゃうと
Are you going to a different hotel?
違うホテル行っちゃうの?
I can't open my ears.
耳が開かない
hot.
熱い
Also, I'm really sweating.
あとすごいなんか汗かいてるよ
That's amazing.
すげえじゃん
Isn't that amazing?
すげえじゃんじゃない
Let me show you something from Gangcheon.
ちょっとカンチョンから見せて
copper?
どう?
Nice, today's Gangchon.
いいね、今日のカンチョン
picture?
え?
It's dirty.
汚れてる
Look.
見て
It's dirty.
汚れてる
Look here.
ほら見て
It's dirty.
汚れてる
Look, look.
見て、ほら
Not dirty.
汚れてない
picture?
え?
It's dirty.
汚れてる
It's dirty, isn't it?
汚れてるでしょ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you tired today?
今日のお疲れ?
picture?
え?
Today's.
今日の
Oh, wait.
え、待って
How tired are you today?
今日のお疲れ具合が
I'm not tired.
お疲れてない
You can see how tired you are here.
お疲れ具合がここに出てるよ
hey.
ね
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
copper?
どう?
this.
これ
It's dirty.
汚 れてるよ
The parts are also bad.
パーツも悪いね
Is it okay?
いいの?
No, but it's not that dirty.
いや、でもそんなに汚れてないんだよね
Yeah, it's not that dirty.
うん、そんなに汚れてない
Yes, take it then.
はい、じゃあ持って
Where did it get dirty?
どこ汚れちゃった?
picture?
え?
Where did it get dirty?
どこ汚れちゃった?
No, I guess I caught it from earlier?
いや、さっきのでついちゃったのかな?
Well, probably so.
いや、多分そうだね
It was beautiful.
綺麗だったもんね
Oh, was it beautiful?
え、綺麗だったの?
Look good.
上手く見てて
Oh my gosh, I'm already sweating in the middle.
やばい、もう中央汗かいてる
Welcome.
ぶっていらっしゃい
picture?
え?
Welcome.
ぶっていらっしゃい
It's falling.
落ちるね
No, wait.
やだ、待って
picture?
え?
Take a look.
ちょっと見て
Nice, buponpon.
いいね、ぶっぽんぽん
Oh no, I'm pissed.
やばい、むちわってる
Isn't that a lie?
嘘でしょ?
Is it that hot?
そんなに熱いの?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, this guy.
じゃあ、こいつ
It was definitely dirty though.
絶対汚かったんだけど
You're tiny too, really.
お前もちっちゃいんだよね、本当に
Same as always though.
相変わらずだけど
Yeah.
うん
Well, it was too much.
まあそう、なくすぎた
Is it correct?
当たってる?
Please, this won't hurt, right?
これ、どうぞ、痛くないでしょ?
Has it arrived?
届い?
where?
どこ?
This is it.
これじゃん
I'm sure you'll know.
絶対、知っちゃうよね
Is it correct?
当たってる?
Can it be conveyed?
伝わる?
Yeah.
うん
Which one?
どっち?
Hey.
ちゃっ
picture?
え?
I cried too much.
泣くすぎた
It's definitely about time.
そろそろ絶対です
Does it feel better inside?
中のほうが気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Does it feel better inside?
中 のほうが気持ちいいの?
I'll be using this a little later,
これ、ちょっと後で使っていくんだけど、
But, I can't get in yet,
でもさ、まださ、入んないからさ、
Isn't it okay to add a little Lawson to this?
これ、ちょっとローソンつけて入れていいじゃん?
No, that's definitely painful.
いや、まあそれ絶対痛いよ
picture?
え?
it hurts?
痛い?
Does it hurt?
痛いかな?
No, it definitely hurts.
いや、絶対それ痛いよ
Does it hurt a little?
ちょっと痛い?
No, no.
いや、いや
No, tell me if it hurts.
いや、痛かったら言って
This definitely hurts.
絶対これ痛いよ
picture?
え?
That definitely hurts.
絶対痛いよ、それ
Does it hurt?
痛いかな?
it hurts.
痛い
Well, tell me if it hurts.
じゃあ、痛かったら言って
No, it definitely hurts.
いや、絶対痛いもん
Well then, I'll get you some Lawson.
じゃあ、ちゃんとローソンつけてあげる
Have you ever put it in yourself?
自分に入れたことある?
picture?
え?
Have you ever put it in yourself?
自分に入れたことある?
this?
これ?
How do I put it in?
どうやって入れるの?
I don't know.
わからない
Put it in with a hole.
穴で入れる
It's a joke, right?
ネタでしょ、今の
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
This is new, so this.
これ新品だから、これ
I haven't used it once yet.
まだ一回も使ってない
It hurts, isn't it?
痛いよね
If I put something that would definitely hurt.
絶対痛いやつ入れたらそう
it hurts?
痛い?
Yeah.
うん
This is definitely painful.
絶対痛いよ、これ
You want to see a dog that hasn't taken a bath.
お風呂入ってないおわんこ見たいんだよね
Hey, it's tiny.
てか、ちっちゃ
Really.
ほんとに
Wow, was this a big bowl?
あれ、こんなおわんこちっちゃかったっけ?
It's small though.
ちっちゃいけどさ
Hey, that looks painful.
ねえ、痛そう
picture?
え?
This might not fit.
これ入んないかも
I won't come in.
入んないよ
Small.
ちっちゃい
It's already gone.
もうちっちゃい
Can we compare?
比較できるかな?
I can't enter.
入れない
I can't get in, that.
入れなくいる、それ
Oh, it's really scary, scary.
え、ほんと怖い、怖い
Tell me if it hurts.
痛かったら言って
No, no, no.
いやだ、いやだ、いやだ
It really, really hurt.
ほんと、ほんと、痛かった
No, really.
いや、ほんとに
No, no, no.
いや、 いや、いやだ
It hurts.
痛いよ
Because it doesn't hurt.
痛くないから
Oh, wait, that hurts.
え、待って、痛いよ
No, that's still in your imagination.
いや、それ、まだ想像の中でしょ
No, no, no, no.
いや、いや、いや、いや
Oh, so scary.
え、こわっとこわっと
No, I really don't like it.
いや、ほんとやだやだ
Make it bigger and then fit it all in.
大きくしてから 全部入る
what?
なに?
Same feeling.
これと同じ感覚
Oh, really, no, no.
え、ほんと、いや、やだ
I've never included that.
それ入れたことないんだけど
it hurts?
痛い?
It might be okay if this hurts.
これが痛かったらいいないかも
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Wait a minute, I don't know.
ちょっと待って、分かんない
Was it painful?
痛 かった?
I wish I could calm down, but...
落ち着いたらいいんだけどさ、それなんか...
Ah, impossible, impossible, impossible.
あ、無理無理無理
Eh, wait, it's impossible, it's impossible.
え、待って、無理無理無理
Impossible, impossible, impossible.
無理無理無理無理
Seriously impossible, seriously impossible.
マジ無理マジ無理
Look, I don't know if it feels good from there.
ほら、そこの方から気持ちいいとか分かんない
Please.
どうかね
No, I don't know?
いや、分かんない?
Wait, wait, wait.
まって、まっすがちじゃん
I put it in for the first time.
初めて入れたよ
This is something that feels good, something to put in.
これ 気持ちいいやつ、入れるやつだもん
This feels so good.
すごい気持ちいいんだよ、これ
I don't know, I don't know.
分かんない分かんない
What, don't you feel it?
え、気持ちくないの?
copper?
どう?
I don't know.
分かんない
picture?
え?
Oh, that feels really weird.
あ、マジ変な感じだね
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
It's decreasing tremendously.
すごい減ってる
What does it feel like?
なんだ感じ?
I don't know.
分かんない
I don't feel anything.
何も感じないです
Oh, that's a lie, right?
え、嘘でしょ?
Are you unsentimental?
不感傷なの?
不感傷?
I'm not numb, but I don't feel anything.
不感傷じゃないけど、何も感じないんだけど
this?
これ?
Aren't you friends?
仲間じゃないの?
I don't understand.
分 か んない
It feels good when I calm down, but this doesn't feel good?
落ち着いたら気持ちいいけど、 これ気持ちよくない?
Is this no good?
これダメ?
No good.
ダメなやつ
Relax a little.
ちょっと緩めて
Loosen, twist, twist.
緩めてねじってねじって
Oh, that.
え、それ
This is the same.
これ同じ
Same feeling.
同じ感じ
Impossible, impossible, impossible.
無理無理無理
It's okay if it hurts.
痛かったらいい
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
痛い痛い痛い
It doesn't hurt, yet.
痛くないでしょ、まだ
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
痛い痛い痛い
TRUE?
本当?
Really, really.
本当本当本当に
本当 に本当に
It really doesn't hurt.
本当に痛くない
it hurts?
痛い?
that.
それ
It hurts.
痛いよ
Does it hurt already?
もう痛い?
I haven't hit it yet.
当たってないよ、まだ
It doesn't hurt, right?
痛くないでしょ
It hurts to wait.
待って痛い
It's all the way to the back.
奥まででしょ
to this point.
ここまで
It's okay if this is the case.
これだったら大丈夫
It doesn't hurt, right?
痛くないでしょ
This definitely doesn't hurt.
絶対痛くないもん、これ
It doesn't hurt.
痛くないんだって
picture?
え?
what?
何?
It's getting early.
早くなってきた
what?
何?
allergy?
アレルギー?
It doesn't hurt, at all.
痛くないし、全然
why?
なんで?
Where?
どこが?
Maybe it's because of my hair.
髪のせいかな
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It doesn't hurt at all.
全然痛くないし
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
feeling?
気持ち?
Don't you feel?
気持ちくない?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
it hurts.
痛い
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
How does it feel?
ど んな感じ?
It feels like something is in there.
なんか入ってる感じ
Do you feel like it's in there?
入ってる感じする?
Hold it a little, yourself.
ちょっと押さえてて、自分で
where?
どこ?
At the bottom.
下のところ
Hold it down.
押さえててね
here?
ここ?
Please have it.
持っててね
Okay.
いいよ
it hurts.
痛い
Do you have this?
これいる?
it hurts?
痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
it hurts.
痛い
Does this hurt?
これ痛い?
It hurts, really.
痛いよ、本当に
Hold me down.
押さえてて
Please have it.
持っててね
I'll bring a light.
ライト持ってくるから
It's really difficult.
すげえ難しい
it hurts.
痛い
What kind of feeling?
どんな感覚?
It's really difficult.
すげえ難しい
I'll show you what's inside.
中を見せるって
Can you see it?
見えるかな?
It's starting to look amazing
すげえ見えてきて
Ru.
る
I saw it.
見 えた
見えた
What I saw inside.
見えた中が
That's amazing.
すごいよ
terrible.
やばい
Want to see it?
見たい?
I don't want to see it.
見たくない
There's a lot of white stuff in there.
なんか白いの入ってるいっぱい
You came here to cum, right?
中出すした来たでしょ?
You cum inside me, right?
中出すしたでしょ?
I haven't.
してないよ
There's a lot of white stuff in there.
白いの入ってるいっぱい
It's full of white liquid.
白い液がいっぱい入ってる
Isn't everyone in there?
みんな入ってるんじゃない?
It's not damp, is it?
湿ないんだよね
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
There's no humidity.
湿がないんだよね
No humidity.
湿がない
it hurts?
痛い?
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
Are you okay.
大丈夫
it hurts?
痛い?
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
That hurts.
それ痛い
mysterious.
神秘的な
It hurts.
痛いよ
Does this hurt?
これ痛い?
it hurts?
痛い?
Let's bring it back.
戻そう
When should I take it out?
いつ抜くの?
Pull it out.
抜く
Do I have to remove it?
抜かなくていい?
Let's pull it out.
抜こうよ
Because the mango is small.
マンゴーちっちゃいからさ
I pulled it out.
抜いたし
thank you.
ありがとう
It was amazing.
すごかった
That's true.
ありだね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Damn, that's amazing.
くすこすげえわ
Will you pull it out?
抜くね?
I'll just pull it out.
抜くんだけどさ
It might hurt.
痛いかもしれない
Please be patient.
我慢してね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Hold on for a moment.
一瞬我慢して
Please hold on for a moment.
一瞬我慢してね
Don't do it all at once.
一気にやらないでよ
Does it cause momentary pain?
一瞬の痛みを伴うのか?
Or does it come gradually?
それともじわじわ伴うのか?
Sober once.
一回地味に
Plainly?
地味に?
What about plainness?
地味にとってもどうなの?
Slowly slowly?
ゆっくりゆっくり?
I'll close it first.
まず閉じるよ
slowly closing
ゆっくり閉じていく
from.
から
Was it painful?
痛 かった?
It didn't hurt though.
痛くなかったけど
I heard a painful sound.
痛そうな音聞こえた
You're chewing right now.
今 噛んでるね
it hurts?
痛い?
It's fixed.
固まってる
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Impossible, impossible, impossible.
無 理無理無理
I'm not stuck though.
引っかかってないんだけど
Should I leave it like this?
このまま抜けばいいのか?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It slipped out.
抜けた
it hurts?
痛い?
Which one?
どっち?
Can I take it out?
抜いていい?
Shall I pull it out?
抜いちゃう?
It's totally okay.
全然大丈夫
look?
見る?
it hurts?
痛い?
white.
白い
I was prepared.
覚悟した
What is that?
なにそれ?
What is this?
なにこれ?
Is it white?
白いの?
I was prepared for it to be white.
白いの覚悟してきたよ
Have you caught it?
捕まえてきた?
What is this?
なにこれ?
これなに?
still?
静止?
What is this?
なにこれ?
Does it not match the pen?
ペンと合わない?
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
I don't know.
分からない
Isn't it dirty?
汚れじゃない?
Is it today for one day?
一日分の今日なの?
Is it difficult when other people are watching?
人が見てると難しい?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I say I'm alone.
一人だと言うんだけど
I'll be alone.
一人になるよ
Where are you going?
どっか行っちゃう?
Okay, let's go somewhere.
いいよ、どっか行っちゃう
How can I do that?
どうしたらできるの?
I don't know.
分からない
I'll watch it, so do it.
見ててあげるからやって
I hate it when I see it.
見てたら嫌だよ
You can't go out.
お出かけしていけないよ
You're stuck in the bathroom.
トイレにこもってるね
You can turn off the sound.
音が切っていいよ
Got it.
分かった
I played music.
音楽かけた
I'll bring you dinner.
ごはんごはん持ってくるから
I'll bring you dinner
ごはんごはん持ってく
Because.
る から
Really.
ほんとにさ
Even though the hardware is expensive.
ハードが高いのに
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
copper?
どう?
This embarrassing appearance.
この恥ずかしい姿
Can I put my penis in it?
チンチン入れちゃっていい?
Isn't this how you get in?
これで入るんじゃねえの?
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
here?
ここ?
Wait, ticklish.
待って、くすぐさ
Did you make this?
これ作った?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Get in?
入れ?
Let me in.
入れよ
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
why?
なんで?
Just put it in there.
どばなく入れよ
It's no different than this.
これと変わらないじゃん
change.
変わる
It won't change.
変 わらないよ
Because it's amazing.
すごいんだから
It's totally amazing.
全 くすごいんだよ
cold.
冷たい
It's too sudden.
いきなりすぎる
cold.
冷たい
I have to open it properly.
ちゃんと開いてないと
It feels amazing.
すげえ気持ちいい
This is dangerous.
やばいんだよこれ
There's a lot in there, isn't it?
すごい入ってるでしょ
Ching Ching.
チ ンチン
I don't understand.
分かんないよね
copper?
どう?
Don't you feel like there's something in there?
チンチン入ってる気がしない?
Yeah.
うん
Chin chin look.
チンチンほら
Is Chin Chin better?
チンチンのほうがいいの?
Chin Chin is better.
チンチンのほうがいいな
It seems like I really don't understand.
ほんと分かんないそうね
What are you saying?
何言ってんの?
Are you really saying that?
ほんとに言ってんの?
It's starting to feel better.
もっと気持ちよくなってるよ
But that was just now.
でもさっきなんだよ
Look.
ほ ら
It's amazing.
すげえ入ってる
It comes in double.
ダブルで入ってるよ
picture?
え?
Look at the double.
ダブルでほら
It's a great double.
すごいダブルで入ってるよ
copper?
どう?
It tickles me.
くすぐっちゃう
You're becoming more charismatic.
カ リスマになってきたね
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'll do this now.
もうこっちやっちゃう
Don't say it hurts.
痛いって言わないで
痛 いって言わないで
why?
なんで?
Cry.
泣いて
If it really hurts, I cry.
本当に痛かったら涙流す
Aren't your hands so sweaty?
手汗すごくない?
Doesn't chin chin hurt?
チンチンは痛くない?
Doesn't it hurt a lot?
チンチン痛くない?
Does it feel good?
チンチン気持ちいい?
Shall I pull it out?
抜いちゃう?
give?
あげる?
Look.
見てよ
It's not okay.
はいはいじゃないよ
Play around with it yourself.
いじって自分で
What should I do?
どう する?
Huh?
あれ?
I didn't understand.
わかんなくなってたよ
How did you know?
なんで分かったの?
If it's this way.
こっちだと
I know how to stop it.
止め方はよく分かったね
A lot of white stuff came out of my pussy.
マンコから白いのがいっぱい出てきちゃった
What is it?
なんだろう?
Don't you know?
知らないの?
What is this?
これ何?
Don't you know?
知らないの?
What is this?
これ何?
The feelings of all the women.
女性のみなさんの気持ち
What is this?
これ何ですか?
これ何?
The white one with lots of it.
いっぱい付いてる白いのが
That's amazing.
すごいね
what happened?
どうしたの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Do you want dick?
チンチン欲しい?
want.
欲しい
Dick?
おちんぽ?
Do you want a dick?
おちんぽ欲しい?
I want a dick.
おちんぽ欲しい
Do a shirt.
シャツやってよ
Let me take it off a little.
ちょっと脱がせてよ
Can't you take it off like that?
そうやって脱がせない?
yes.
はい
Panpon?
パンポン?
pants?
パンツ?
Ching Ching?
チンチン?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Let me take it off with the skin on.
皮を被った状態で脱がせて
This will grow.
これ伸びるね
That's amazing, isn't it?
すごいでしょ
pants?
パンツ?
It looks like maple bread, right?
かえぱんっぽいでしょ
Leave it as is.
そのままで
Lick it good.
いいの舐めて
covered with skin.
皮を被った状態で
Leave it like this?
このまま?
For now.
とりあえずね
It goes really deep.
す げー奥まで入る
すげー奥まで入るね
Deeper.
もっと奥まで
From here?
ここから?
From here.
ここからね
I won't sit down for a while.
ちょっと座らないからね
Give me your hand.
手を出してね
You won't take it.
取らないでしょ
That doesn't happen.
それはなるくないんだよ
In your mouth.
くわえて
Park.
パク
Wait a minute, it's huge.
ちょっと待って、でかい
huge?
でかい?
Huge
でかいで
Sho.
しょ
Let's understand a little.
ちょっと 通じてね
This 2.
これ2
this?
これ?
Is that then?
それじゃあなの?
Is that no good?
それじゃあダメ?
Ah, that's nice.
あ、それいいね
It's here.
ここだよね
Okay.
いいよ
Jiggle more and more.
もっともっとプルプルして
ice cream.
アイスクリーム
Ice cream?
アイスクリーム?
oh yeah.
そうそう
This is ice cream.
これアイスクリームだね
oh yeah.
そうそう
That side.
その辺
Hide.
隠って
Yeah.
うん
lens.
レンズ
There's a round lens on the lens.
あるでしょ、レンズに丸いのが
Don't look here.
ここ見ないで
Okay, see you then.
よし、じゃあさ
Yeah.
うん
Should I go to bed?
ベッドに行こうかな
I wonder if there will be an extra?
おまけ入るかな
Yeah.
うん
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃう?
Would you like to try it?
入れてみる?
From before.
前から
Can I just put it in like this?
このまま入れるの?
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
They're the same type.
タイプから一緒だな
Both sides.
横とも
Wait, where is it from here?
待って、どこだ、ここからだ
Is it your type?
タイプか?
copper?
どう?
In summer, I sweat easily.
夏、すぐ汗かく
熱
stomach.
い
It's hot.
熱 い
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
hot.
熱い
Would you like to come in?
入 ってみる?
hot.
熱い
Shall I put it in?
入れちゃう?
Would you like to come in?
入ってみる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
hot.
熱い
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
So, make your own.
じゃあ、自分のくりいじって
Because it feels good to play around with.
気持ちよくいじってるから
Yeah,
うん、
Play with it comfortably.
気 持ちよくいじって
I'm sleeping a lot
あんま寝てる
Na.
な
I'm looking at you.
み っちゃみっちゃ見てるよ
hot.
熱い
hot?
熱い?
Yeah.
うん
In the back?
奥の?
Is it better in the back?
奥のほうがいい?
It's better in the back.
奥のほうがいい
What should I do?
どうすればいい?
Well, I'm sleeping.
あ ん ま寝てるから
I want to go by Rhodes Royce.
ロードスロイスで行きたいんだよね
ロ ードスロイスで行きたい
I'm sleeping a lot.
あんま寝てる
It grows so much.
めっちゃ育っちゃう
Give me your hand?
手ちょうだい?
Give me your hand.
手ちょうだい
I have some sleeping clothes on.
なんか寝物のついてる
Okay, then let's type.
よっしゃ、じゃあタイプいっちゃうよ
w
Ah, that's hot...
あー、 熱い...
It was really intense at the end...
最後、めっちゃ激しかった...
Wow, that's hot...
は ー、熱い...
How did you do it?
どうやった?
最後...
It's already too intense, already...
もう激しすぎて、もう...
That's dangerous...
ヤバい...
Yeah, a momentary incident...
うん、一瞬の出来事を...
Okay!
よし!
Wait a minute...
ちょ待ってねー...
How did you do it?
どうやった?
Just like this...
このまま...
How did you do it?
どうやった?
Just like this... like this...
このまま...このまま....
Just like that...just like that, I was able to cross...
そのまま...そのまま、渡れてきた...
Okay, leave it as is.
いいよ、そのままね
I've been eating.
食べてきた
Okay, I put it out.
いいよ、出したよ
Show me your face.
見せて、こっち顔
Face from below.
下から顔
Look, it's here.
ほら、あるじゃん、ここに
Look, can you see this camera?
見て、こっちのカメラ見える?
appear.
見える
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
It's coming out, see.
出てきてるよ、ほら
You've been eating, haven't you?
食べてきてるでしょ?
Isn't it great?
すごくね?
A lot of electrons came out.
めっちゃ電子出てきた
It's out.
出ましたね
Show me the inside of your pussy, right there.
おまんこの中見せて、そこで
That's fine, right there.
そこでいいよ、そこで
Go, slowly.
行 けよ、ゆっくり
Take it slow.
ゆっくりね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Look, I'm already in.
ほら、もう入った
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
I'll go slowly.
ゆ っくり行くよ
Oh, I can't see it.
あー、見えない
It's dark and I can't see.
暗くて見えない
I have a lot of semen on my hands,
手に精子めっちゃついてるんだけど、
Sample sample.
検体さまる
What do you think?
どうだろう?
Can you see it?
見えるかな?
It's in.
入ってんね
What?
何が?
There's a lot in it.
めっちゃ入ってんじゃん
How do I guess this?
これどうやって当てるんだろう?
That's difficult.
難しいな
No, this is difficult.
いや、これ難しいな
It's inside, try moving your pussy.
入ってる、おまんこ動かしてみて
picture?
え?
Can you move your pussy?
おまんこ動かせる?
From there.
そこから
I think you should laugh.
笑えばいいと思う
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い、痛い
Did you move it?
動かした?
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い、痛い
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, when it moves.
あー、動くと
I have to move a lot.
あんま動かないとね
It's hot.
熱いね
Wow, there's sperm inside.
すごい、中に精子がある
Okay.
よし
Well then, I'll cry.
じゃ、泣くね
No, the sperm has stopped.
いや、精子さまったね
When I smile, that's how it comes out.
笑うとね、そう出てきちゃう
Okay, then that's the last pose.
よし、じゃあ最後そのポーズで
how was it?
どうだった?
thoughts.
感想
thoughts?
感想?
It felt so good.
すごく気持ちよかった
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
Was it too confusing at the end?
最後はぎしすぎたかな?
It's so intense at the end that I feel like I'll be crying in no time.
最後はぎすぎて、もう一瞬で泣き終わるみたいな
Sorry.
ごめんね
I'll cry slowly.
ゆっくり泣くからね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Good.
よいしょ
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's so messed up.
めっちゃくちゃくちゃ
Thank you for your hard work.
お疲れさまでした
Well, let's pay for two drinks.
じゃあ、2杯払おう
I'll pay for two drinks this time.
今度は2杯払おう
Pussy.
おまんこ
Finally, try a burger with a double piece towards your pussy.
最後、おまんこに向かって、 ダブルピースでバーガーしよう
bye bye.
バイバイ
good night.
おやすみなさい
Let's do it again.
またやろうね
See you then.
じゃあ ね
Good night, bye-bye.
おやすみ、バイバイ